The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Twenty-Eighth Episode
The Iron Lion
Sapphire, blinded,
was taken away by Mephisto.
But then, saved by Hecate,
she learned that the King and the Queen...
...were on the Island of Serpents,
transformed into stone statues.
While trying to save them,
she fell into the sea.
She is saved by the pirate Blood.
With him, she goes to the Magic Spring
to heal her eyes.
Thanks to the magic water of the
spring, she regains her sight...
...and with the pirate Blood's ship
she sets off for Coolland...
..to fight
Queen Icicle.
And now, enjoy
"The Iron Lion."
The Island of Serpents!
There is the Island of Serpents!
Father...
Mother...
Here I am, safe and sound,
thanks to your protection...
...and that of a friend
once helped.
You know how much I want to help you
but even if I came there,
now I could do nothing for you.
Without the help of Mephisto
I cannot break...
...this infamous spell
that holds you prisoner.
Now I must try to thwart
the plans of Queen Icicle,
sovereign of Coolland.
And I must hurry!
Wait until I have
accomplished this. Be patient!
Listen, father, mother...
You'll see that I will soon defeat
the damned Queen Icicle!
Take something to offer as a tribute
to Queen Icicle!
Yes, sir!
- If you take this away from me...
- That! Give it to me!
No... Please!
Leave it to me!
- Give it back to me!
- Grandpa! Grandpa!
Make way! Queen Popsicle is
waiting for us! Let's go, quickly!
- What a shame!
- It's not possible!
Dammit! Take it to the
Queen with my compliments!
They come day and night
to steal the merchandise...
...and they always steal from
me because it's the finest!
What thieves!
Hello! Good morning everyone!
This fruit looks delicious. Tell
me, how much does it cost?
You want to know how much it costs? Well,
then you aren't one of those from the castle!
No, indeed!
I am the ghost knight!
The ghost knight!
Welcome!
For you, this fruit is the best
and cheapest in all of Coolland!
And what would be different
if I came from the castle?
I'll tell you, ghost knight!
The Queen's soldiers and followers
never pay!
That's why Grandpa and everyone
else are always angry!
What?! They don't pay?
Is she that stingy, this Queen?
- Watch out!
- If we speak ill of the Queen
the soldiers arrest us! Therefore
it's better not to talk about it at all!
Silence!
You know the Queen's
orders well!
You know what happens to those
who speak ill of her, don't you?
Please forgive me!
I only said what
crossed my mind.
Shut up! Shut up! One must not
disobey the laws of Coolland!
Forgive me, please!
- Grandpa, you don't have to apologize!
- What do you want to do?
If you really want to know what
I want to do, I'll tell you right now!
- I want to fight you!
- Hurrah!
And if you want to hear me
speak ill of the Queen, here you go!
Damn the Queen of Coolland!
She is stupid, fat, and dumb!
Curse you!
I won't let you talk like that!
Step forward!
Come at me!
- Hurrah!
The soldier of Coolland
isn't as strong as he seems!
He's not strong, he's a coward!
To hell with it!
Get him!
Get him, dead or alive!
Stop!
How they exaggerate! It's
as if they were really at war.
Damn! Someone's coming!
Let's hope they don't see me!
Why don't we try
to set a trap for him?
Listen, you, go back to the market immediately.
If the ghost knight
should arrive,
observe him closely and follow him,
but discreetly, understood?
Discreetly,
but you must investigate thoroughly!
- Yes, of course! Alright!
- I think I know that guy.
I see, he was at the market!
I didn't think
there was a spy there too!
That's how they manage
to find out so quickly...
...who speaks ill of the Queen!
What a terrible country!
This is a particularly
delicate moment...
...and we must be
very careful,
because of this new weapon
that we've just made!
So you did it,
the iron lion!
Shut up! Don't speak so loudly!
- You can go now.
- See you!
I'm counting on you, my friends,
work with great care!
- And who are you?
- Come on, Gelo, don't make such a fuss!
Take me to see the new weapon right away!
You must be the ghost knight!
How young you are!
Follow me!
So many barrels are here!
They are all full of the wine needed
for the inhabitants of the castle.
The new weapon is down here!
How strange this underground road is!
It’s coming!
Hey, what is this piece of iron?
What? Do you really
not know it? It’s a train!
Come on, get on with me!
- Are you afraid, ghost knight?
- Of course not!
If I can reach the new weapon
with this train, then I'm getting on!
I think I've seen you
somewhere else before!
No, you're quite mistaken.
It's the first time I've seen you.
Damn, look how fast it's going!
But that's Tink!
Oh, yeah?! I can jump too!
Down!
And what's this?
The siren!
They're looking for me!
You still haven't found
that damned ghost knight!
Come on, you slackers, look
for him! Search thoroughly!
The Queen is arriving!
Welcome, my Queen!
Welcome, Your Majesty!
Gelo, I thank you for the work you've done!
I heard that you've completed
the new weapon. Where is it?
Take me there immediately,
I'm very impatient to see it.
- Yes, of course!
- It's that way, Majesty!
I'm afraid the ghost knight might arrive!
Move it!
How beautiful!
It's wonderful, Gelo!
And how does this iron lion work?
Would you please explain it to me?
Look at the hole on the lion's forehead!
From that hole, with the power of steam,
- a hundred arrows are being launched!
- A hundred arrows?
Yes! With them we will be able to
break through the walls of any castle!
- Then test it right now!
- Test it?
Line up the prisoners under
the cliff and try to knock it down!
Weapons are completely
useless if they don't kill people!
Let the lion assist
in the execution!
- Send the laziest ones!
- Yes!
How cruel the Queen is!
Oh! Tink is there too!
Look at him, please! Do you
see how the steam is coming out?
Sapphire, where are you?
Father who art in heaven, help me!
I’m going to die and I don't want to!
Ready...!
- The Ghost Knight!
- The Ghost Knight?!
That's Sapphire! Let's go!
But what are you doing here, Tink?
Those damn soldiers
brought me here on the train!
- My Queen, are you alright?
- What are you doing?
It's time to put the power
of the iron lion to the test!
Go! Fire the arrows!
What power!
Admirable, Gelo!
The Ghost Knight must
have been blown to pieces!
- I really hope so!
- He is definitely dead!
Anyway,
cursed ghost knight
before dying
you were able to experience my power!
Listen, soldiers,
I beg you to give me your lives!
Fight for the cause
of your Queen!
My heart is always
in your hearts!
Let's go to Silverland! Let's show them
how strong we are!
Stop! Everyone look!
From here we can see Silverland.
As soon as you pass the hill
head inland!
Sapphire, they are coming!
We must prevent the iron lion
from entering Silverland!
Father, mother,
please, protect me.
This arrow
will decide the fate of Silverland!
Sapphire! There it is!
What is happening?
It's turning back!
How is it possible? What are you all doing?
Go forward! Fight!
Hooray!
Well done, it's retreating!
We won!
I beat the iron lion!
Let's retreat!
Tink!
Tink is dead!
Tink, I'm so sorry!
But I'm sure
that you went straight to heaven!
- Sapphire!
- Who is it? Who are you?
- Hecate!
- I have been looking for you for a long time!
I wanted to warn you that your
father and your mother are in danger!
- What?!
- Are they in danger?!
- My father is furious and has
threatened to tear the statues to pieces.
- Oh, God!
- I can't stop him anymore!
My father won't calm
down until you go to him.
- Then I will go at once.
Take me there, Hecate!
- But if you go there, he will
steal your heart, you know it!
- I am prepared for even that!
Take me to the Island of Serpents!
All right.
If you really want to, follow me!
But is Tink, Sapphire's best friend, really dead?
What will become of Sapphire,
persecuted by the Queen of Coolland and by Mephisto?
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP